jdsports.co.uk 2011-06-19

# Privacy - JD Sports UK

We (JD Sports Fashion Plc ) are committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy explains what personal information is collected from you via this Web Site and what we do with that information. It forms part of our terms and conditions, which we may amend from time to time. By using this Web Site you agree to the way in which we process your personal information as outlined in this policy.

### Information collected

We collect personal information from you when you register with us, complete an on-line form, you e-mail us or complete a transaction with us, you enter a prize draw or other competition with us, or we speak to you over the telephone.   
We also collect personal information about you by using "cookies" on our Web Site - please see the section on cookies below.  
We collect the following information about you in order to process our orders: your name, address, delivery address (if different), credit or debit card number and expiry date. We also ask for a telephone number to contact you if there are any difficulties with your order.

### Use of information

We use the information we collect about you to process orders, deal with any enquiry or request and/or to send you information about our products and offers from time to time.  
Your credit card details are taken through a secure server for processing by your card provider, our card processor and our bank. Please see our terms and conditions for details of the measures we take to try and ensure the security of your data.  
We will pass your name and delivery address on to the carrier responsible for delivering your order.   
We may also use the information that we collect to inform you about new products, offers or changes to our products. If you would prefer not to receive any marketing information, please send an e-mail to [onlinehelp@jdplc.com](mailto:onlinehelp@jdplc.com).  
The information collected about you will not be used for any other purposes and will not be sold or otherwise disclosed to any other organisations, except to (i) other companies within our group, (ii) our or their successors in title and (iii) third party service providers engaged by us (or other members of our group) to help operate our business effectively.   
From time to time your personal information may be processed by systems which are located outside the United Kingdom. Where this happens, we will ensure that your information will be kept secure and your privacy rights remain protected consistent with the Data Protection Act 1998.

### Cookies - Collection of Anonymous Data

As described above, we sometimes collect anonymous information from visits to our site to help us provide better customer service. For example, we keep track of the domains from which people visit and we also measure visitor activity on this Web Site, but we do so in ways that keep the information anonymous. We use the information that we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different areas of our Web Site, and to help us make our Web Site more useful to visitors. This includes analysing these logs periodically to measure the traffic through our servers, the number of pages visited and the level of demand for pages and topics of interest. The logs may be preserved indefinitely and used at any time and in any way to prevent security breaches and to ensure the integrity of the data on our servers.  
We collect the anonymous information we mentioned above through the use of various technologies, one of which is called "cookies". A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard drive.

### Customer/User Identification and Log-In

A temporary cookie is currently used to identify a user during the registration and checkout processes.  
When a user provides a username (email address) and password to "log into" this Web Site, either as an existing or a new user, a temporary cookie is set which identifies the applicable user account.  
This temporary cookie is maintained until the user:  
1. Clicks the log out button  
2. Closes down their browser session  
3. Manually clears the User identification cookie

### User Log-In Caching

Within this Web Site cookies may in the future be used to save the visitor's password (if and when this facility is provided) so that it does not have to be re-entered at each new visit.  
If the user has chosen "remember login and password", the following two items above will be encoded within cookies:  
Â· A unique Customer ID   
Â· A login state  
If a "registered" user to this Web Site returns to the site without logging in, the ID stored in the cookie can be used to track the user (unless the user manually deleted the cookie, at which point the server may automatically regenerate another cookie).

### Basket Functionality

This Web Site also utilises cookies for the identification of baskets. When a user clicks an 'Add to Basket' button for the first time during a browsing session a temporary cookie is set to identify a unique Basket ID for that user.  
Any items that the user chooses to add to the basket are associated with the unique Basket ID until the user either:  
1\. Closes down their browser session  
2\. Places an order  
3\. Removes all items from their current basket  
4\. Manually clears the Basket Cookie  
The temporary cookie is cleared when any of the above events occur.

### Basket Caching

This Web Site may, at some point in the future utilise non-temporary cookies or (i.e. having a limited or unlimited lifespan) to enable basket identifiers to be stored for longer than a single browsing session.   
Non-temporary cookies would only be used to enhance the user experience and avoid the need for new basket identifiers to be issued during each new user session.  
Non-temporary basket cookies would remain until the user:  
1. Places an order  
2. Removes all items from their current basket  
3. Manually clears the Basket Cookie

### Collection and Anonymous Usage of Personal Data

When we collect personal data from you in connection with a transaction we may extract some information about that transaction in an anonymous format and combine it with other anonymous information.  
This anonymous information is used and analysed only at an aggregate level to help us understand trends and patters. None of this information is reviewed at an individual level.  
If you do not want your transaction details used in this manner, you can either disable your cookies or opt-out at the order or request stage.

### Children

**If you are aged under 12 then you can not register, or enter any competitions, on this Web Site.**

### Access Right

You have a right to access the personal information held about you. To obtain a copy of the information, please write to us at;

**Customer Services**  
JD Internet  
JD Sports Fashion Plc  
Hollinsbrook Way  
Pilsworth  
Bury  
BL9 8RR

enclosing a cheque for £10.

### Other web sites

Our Web Site may contain links to other web sites which are outside our control and are not covered by the privacy policy. If you access other sites then using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours.
